RYAN H S

ryan@vloro.com (62) - 85720759240

PROGRAMMER

Profile

Starting as web developer, and have a wide perspective of lots of things in programming. from critical mission C application & cutting-edge web developer to Artificial Intelligence.

Skills

Web Developer

Experienced about 4 years in web development.

C Programmer

Some project need critical mission where C is the best solution. No doubt about it.

Artificial Intelligence

As researcher today, Artificial Intelligence is a trend right now.

Technical

HTML5	Laravel	Linux
Javascript	CodeIgniter	Windows
SASS & LESS	C for Web	

Experience

Pasebandotcom PHP Programmer

April 2011 - December 2011

Start working after doing national exam in vocational high school. as young programmer gain experience.

CV Pusat Link.

January 2012 - March 2012

Full Stack Programmer (System & Web)

Learn become senior programmer. Build complex API server.

CV Techno

March 2012 - August 2012

Full Stack Programmer (System & Web)

Partner company of CV Pusat Link.

PT Topi Putih Kreasi Indonesia

October 2012 - january 2014

Web Programmer, Technical advisor

Learn to be responsible in lots of project.

PT Voxteneo Indonesia

September 2014 - July 2015

PHP Programmer

Learn lots of experience in proffesional attitude and technical knowledge in very large project.

Education

SMKN 4 Bandung - (Vocational High School)

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak (Software Engineering)

STMIK "amikbandung"

Teknik Informatika (Computer Science/Informatics) 3.53 GPA

Institut Teknologi Bandung (ITB)

Teknik Elektro Option Teknik Media Digital dan Game (Master degree) in progress:-)

Awardee

Mahasiswa Program Beasiswa Unggulan, yang Mendapat Prestasi di Bidang Teknologi Informasi

BPKLN Kemdikbud RI 2012

TIM Website Dinas Pendidikan / Penerimaan Peserta Didik Baru (PPDB) Kota Bandung

STMIK "amikbandung" 2013

Volunteer / Open-

CSPY PHP Framework

a minimalist php framework i created in high school :-)

before i know about codeigniter etc.. 2009

source Contribution

CI TPL

an admin system for Codeigniter 2.x, since there is Codeigniter 3 has been released. This is about to dicontinued, only maintain existed project. **2011**

Encylopedia

JS Classes for handling really large data in Javascript, Registered in JS Classes 2015

Genetic Algorithm Toolkit in PHP

toolkit focused on build genetic algorithm application with costumized schema, composer: ryanhs/genetic-algorithm-tooklit **2015**

PPDB Kota Bandung

Yearly event when student apply for Elementary/Junior High School/Senior High School **2011 - now (yearly event)**

TIM Website Dinas Pendidikan / Penerimaan Peserta Didik Baru (PPDB) Kota Bandung STMIK "amikbandung" **2013**

Seminar
Portfolio
(as speaker)

Hacking Black or White UNPAD 2009

Make Your Linux Powerfull UNPAD 2010

Web Design and Security in 2014 and Web Hacking Demo STMIK "amikbandung" 2013

The Future of Android Universitas Sangga Buana **2014**

Workshop
Portfolio
(as trainer)

Workshop Hacking
STMIK "amikbandung" **08-19 February 2010**

Workshop Hacking STMIK "amikbandung" **01-12 March 2010**

Journal Portfolio Komparasi Algoritma Pengurutan Untuk Penerimaan Peserta Didik Baru Kota Bandung

Tati Suprapti, Ryan Hamonangan - UNJANI (2015)